# Mahmoud Mirani

**.** +46 76 268 1910

in linkedin.com/in/mahmoud-mirani

github.com/MoodMirani

#### **INTRO**

While studying at KTH, I worked parttime in We Know IT, which is a small IT consultancy company. After that I worked as a developer in TeamEngine. My goal is to work at a place where I can create exciting new digital applications and contribute to a fun office culture.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Master of Science in Engineering**

Aug. 2017 - Dec. 2023

University: KTH Royal Institute of Technology

Stockholm

- Major: Interactive Media Technology
- I studied Programming, Algorithms, Machinelearning, Math, Physics and some Economi.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Jan 2023 - September 2023 **React Developer** 

Company: TeamEnaine

Stockholm

- Learned working with a DevOps workflow while developing a notifications panel in Reactjs including automated Cypress tests.
- The panel has been deployed and is currently being used by thousands of customers who responded with good feedback.

**Head of IT** Jan 2022 - Sept 2022

Company: We Know IT

Stockholm

- I introduced automated testing to our products and wrote documentation for a standardised project plan including set phases for testing and progress reflections. This increased the quality and also reduced our debugging time.
- I specified and wrote documentation for the IT recruitment process to find suitable candidates.
- To lower the development time of each project. I introduced the idea of having an internal coding library and documentation of company standard projectstructures and techstacks. This expanded the knowledge sharing between the developers.

**Regional Director** May 2021 - Jan 2022

Company: We Know IT

Stockholm

- Learned project management as I managed 4 clients, the project with the most value was worth 450 000 SEK.
- I was a boardmember for the strategic leadership of the company, during this year, our revenue grew by 100%, from 2.5M to 5M.
- I was in charge of the recruitment and team in the Stockholm department. My team were 11 Developers and one UI Designer. I learned Agile Software development and Scrum during this time.
- I managed sales in Stockholm, total revenue of which is was responsible for was approximately 650 000 SEK.

**Teaching Assistant** Sept 2020 - May 2021

University: KTH Royal Institute of Technology

Stockholm

KTH

KTH

Helped KTH students with programming and graded their projects. Learned how to communicate efficiently.

### **EXTRACURRICULAR**

# **Boardmember in Bright at KTH**

July 2022 - June 2023

Specific role: Head of IT

 During my year, we tripled the amount of members and became the biggest association at KTH, landing at 1127 members. Apart from that i built a new website and ticketing system to charge students for our event tickets.

## Diverse voluntary roles during my time at KTH:

Sept. 2017 - June. 2023

Organisations: The chapter of Media Technology & The Chapter of OPEN at KTH

- Project Leader for the reception: I learned project management by recruiting a team of 50 students. Planned and coordinated a 4 week long reception for 150 newly admitted students to KTH
- Webmaster for the reception: Lead a group of 4 people with the task of developing and maintaining a website for the reception of the newly admitted students. We used AWS, Flask & Reactis for the website
- PR Manager in Metaspexet: Led a group of 6 people. Our task was to market "Metaspexet 2019: Elementary", which is an interactive theater at KTH. We sold out all 460 tickets.
- Event Manager in the Business Relations Committee: Contacted companies in the IT/management business and planned events with them and our students. We created a total of 4 events.
- Projectgroupmember at Medias Branchdag: My main responsibility was the website and IT related work.
- Accountant: I reviewed the management of the organisation "Sektionen för Medieteknik" at KTH.

# **SKILLS**

Programming Languages: Python, Java, C, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, SQL, Cypress Developer Tools: VS Code, Google Cloud Platform, Android Studio, Firebase, Expo Go

Technologies/Frameworks: ReactJS, Git, Cypress, WordPress, Figma

Languages: Swedish, English, Kurdish